

PROFILE

Versatile Full Stack Developer with 5+ years of experience designing, developing, and managing complex ecommerce sites and service booking websites. Specializes in React JS and responsive websites with interactive features that drive business growth and improve UX.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+92 344 5034029

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/muh ammad89-sajid

EMAIL:

sajid89sahal@gmail.com

HOBBIES:

Surf around the internet to keep myself up to date about the current affairs and technology world. Moreover, I am cricket and badminton player.

SAJID SADDIQUE

Full Stack Developer (React is, Vue is, Laravel)

EDUCATION

BS (IT) – MUST (Mirpur University of Science and Technology (September 2008 – September 2013)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead developer + Product manager (Al Quran classes)

June-current

Responsible for managing a team of developers, SQA and product analysts. Also responsible for developing backend services and managing server.

Senior Full Stack Developer (D4 Interactive)

2020-2023

Responsible for creating, improving and developing on-going IT project strategies. Outlined work plans and wrote timelines. Designed processes for cleanup and performance improvement that minimized downtime.

Full Stack developer (Selteq Itd)

2018-2020

Developed the company's main product (service booking application http://findanexpert.net/) from scratch in React JS .Implemented and integrated APIs, gathered the requirements from the client and decided the timeline. Worked on numerous Word press and PHP web applications and led/managed a team of React and PHP developers. Managed the company's domain servers. Worked with a network and cyber security team member to secure the servers and company's private data.

SKILLS

PHP Laravel, Vue JS, React JS, WooCommerce, Word press Rest API, My Sql database, JavaScript, iQuery and AJAX